gamefools.com 2018-03-03

# Free Online and Download Games - Play Games at GameFools

**Please read this document carefully before accessing the content on this web site.**

GameFools LLC ("GameFools") respects your right to privacy. We understand the sensitive nature of privacy issues and we take appropriate actions to ensure that your confidentiality is protected. GameFools provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our web site practices with respect to the way your information is collected and used. 

**Information Collection and Use**

GameFools is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. GameFools collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's device containing anonymous information about the user. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Cookies do lots of different jobs, like letting you navigate between pages efficiently and remembering your account preferences. They can also help to ensure that advertisements you see online are more relevant to you and your interests. By using the GameFools website, you consent to the placement of the cookies referenced herein. You can, however, set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. 

**Links**

This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that GameFools is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this website. 

**Email Collection**

If you download a game from our website, purchase a game, or sign up for a membership, we may ask for your email address. This information will be used only for the purpose of our email newsletter and will not be shared with any outside parties other than the service provider that delivers our email newsletter. If you do not wish to receive our email newsletter, you may opt-out of receiving it by clicking on the link to do so in the body of the email. GameFools has a strict no-spam policy, and we do not send unsolicited bulk or commercial email under any circumstances. We do not purchase email address lists from any third parties, and we do not sell email address lists to any outside parties. 

**Purchases**

If you make a purchase from us through our site, we will ask you to provide certain information, including your contact details (such as your full name and email address), and your billing information (such as your credit card number and the date that your card expires). We will use this information to process your transaction and to contact you regarding your purchase if necessary. We will share this information with our payment processor to the extent necessary to facilitate your purchase (for purposes such as customer service, verification, fulfillment and billing purposes). We will not sell or rent your personal billing information to any third party. 

**Interactive Features**

If you access user commenting features, other interactive sharing or social features that may be offered through our website and/or services, you should be aware that any personal information you submit, display, or publish there is considered publicly available and can be read, collected, used, and disclosed by other users of those features, by us, and other third parties without restriction, except to the extent limited access features are available, if any. To request removal of such personal information, contact us at the information provided in this Privacy Policy. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

**Third Party Advertising**

Please understand that advertisers or web sites that link to our site may collect personal information about you. The privacy policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, other advertisers or web sites. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our sites. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other sites in order to help them provide relevant ads to users. 

**Google Analytics and Adwords**

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google. Google Analytics uses cookies to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will be transmitted to and stored by Google. This website also uses conversion tracking for Google AdWords. A cookie will be automatically placed if a user clicks on one of the advertisements placed by Google. The cookie information is used to create statistics about the conversion for Google AdWords customers, but none of this information can be used to identify your personal information. 

**Remarketing**

GameFools uses 3rd party vendor remarketing tracking cookies, including the Google Adwords tracking cookie. This means we will continue to show ads to you across the Internet, specifically on the Google Content Network. As always we respect your privacy and are not collecting any identifiable information through the use of Google's or any other 3rd party remarketing system. The third-party vendors, including Google, whose services we use, will place cookies on web browsers in order to serve ads based on past visits to our website. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. This allows us to make special offers and continue to market our services to those who have shown interest in our service. 

**Legal Requirements**

We may disclose personal information if we have a good-faith belief that doing so is required by a subpoena, warrant, or other judicial or administrative order or otherwise required by law. Additionally, we may disclose personal information where we, in good faith, deem it appropriate or necessary to prevent violation of our Terms of Use or End User License Agreements, or our other agreements; take precautions against liability; protect our rights, property, or safety, or those of a partner, any individual or the general public; maintain and protect the security and integrity of our website and/or services or infrastructure; protect ourselves and our website and/or services from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; investigate and defend ourselves against third party claims or allegations; or assist government regulatory agencies. 

**Minors**

We do not knowingly seek or collect personal information from users under the age of 18. Minors are not allowed to create an account without a parent's or guardian's express consent. We recommend that minors ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet. Your continued use of the website and/or services will be considered by GameFools as confirmation that your parent or guardian has expressly consented to the handling of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

**Change of Ownership**

Information about our users, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any bankruptcy, merger, sale, transfer of company assets, acquisition, or similar transaction. In the event of such a transaction in which your personal information would be transferred to a third party, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you. For example, we will post a notice of the transfer of personal information on our website and/or services and, if we have your email address, we will send notice of the transfer of personal information to that email address. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

By using the web site, you signify your understanding of our privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the web site. If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy or any other privacy issues in connection with the web site, please visit customer support or mail your inquiry to: 

GameFools LLC   
1971 East Beltline NE   
Suite 106, Box 119   
Grand Rapids, Michigan 49525   
USA
